The greatest turkey movie of all time.
Free Birds is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Jimmy Hayward.
Two turkeys from opposite sides of the tracks must put aside their differences and team up to travel
back in time to change the course of history—and get turkey off the holiday menu for good.
Reggie (voice), played by Owen Wilson.
Jake (voice), played by Woody Harrelson.
Jenny (voice), played by Amy Poehler.
S.T.E.V.E. (voice), played by George Takei.
Myles Standish (voice), played by Colm Meaney.
Chief Broadbeak (Voice), played by Keith David.
Free Birds is a 2013 American animated Thanksgiving science fiction comedy film directed by
Jimmy Hayward, who co-wrote the screenplay with the film's producer Scott Mosier.
The film stars the voices of Owen Wilson, Woody Harrelson, and Amy Poehler, with
supporting roles by George Takei, Colm Meaney, Keith David, and Dan Fogler.
In the film, two turkeys named Reggie and Jake go back in time to
the first Thanksgiving to get turkeys off the menu.
Free Birds was produced by Reel FX Creative Studios as its 7th full-length animated feature film and Relativity
Media as its 4th animated film after Monster House (2006), The Tale of Despereaux (2008), and 9 (2009).
Originally titled Turkeys, and scheduled for 2014, the film was
released by Relativity Media on November 1, 2013.
Free Birds grossed $110 million worldwide against a $55 million budget
and received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film was nominated for the Annie Award for  Outstanding
Achievement for Music in a Feature Production.
The film explores themes of holiday, freedom,
thanksgiving, duringcreditsstinger, playful.
The tone is lighthearted.